A poisonous fish, which has a sting strong enough to kill a human, is invading the
Mediterranean, warn scientists.
The International Union for the Conservation of Nature has raised concerns after the
poisonous fish was spotted in the waters around Turkey, Cyprus and the Eastern
Mediterranean. The International Union for the Conservation of Nature has raised
concerns after the poisonous fish was spotted in the waters around Turkey, Cyprus
and the Eastern Mediterranean.
Native to the South Pacific and Indian Ocean, the potentially deadly fish has
poisonous hooks and a painful sting capable of killing people.
Native to the South Pacific and Indian Ocean, potentially deadly fish has poisonous
hooks and a painful sting capable of killing people.
Native to the South Pacific and Indian Ocean, the potentially deadly fish has
poisonous hooks and a painful sting capable of killing people.
Although fatalities are rare, the stings can cause extreme pain and stop people
breathing. The fish, often known as devil firefish, is a highly invasive species.
And environmentalists fear its arrival could endanger other types of marine life.
After being spotted in the Mediterranean, a marine scientist says,
fish is spreading, and that's a cause for concern.
And environmentalists fear its arrival could endanger other types of marine life.
After being spotted in the Mediterranean,